incredibots.com 2010-09-24

# IncrediBots - Online Robot Physics Game!

  | 

Last modified: December 30, 2009

IncrediBots.com, IncrediBotsGold.com and IncrediBots2.com (individually and collectively, "IncrediBots") are owned and operated by Big Fish Games, Inc. ("Big Fish Games").  Big Fish Games and the IncrediBots team have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.  **By visiting IncrediBots, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

## INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT 

### Personally Identifiable Information:

We collect no personally identifiable information when you create an IncrediBots account. We may collect the following information if you sign up to become an IncrediBots supporter: 

  * First name, last name, e-mail address, billing address, phone number 
  * credit or debit card information, depending on your form of payment. We do not store any credit card information after your transaction is complete. 

### IP Address:

When a user visits IncrediBots, we may collect the IP address that requested the display of this Web site. 

### Sign Up and Survey information:

Any information you provide to us as part of your use of IncrediBots will be stored as entered. 

### Cookies:

Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by Web sites. Through your Web browser, cookies are only used by the Web site that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from IncrediBots is encrypted and only accessible by the Big Fish Games Web sites. Personal information stored in our cookies is limited to your username and the e-mail address associated with your account. 

## Other Information Collected:

The Web browser or client software that you use to access IncrediBots may transmit certain geographic information and information regarding the capabilities or features of your computer and/or software to us. We may also track other types of information, such as what games users play, how long our users have participated in IncrediBots, the last time a user visited IncrediBots, and whether a user has won any sweepstakes, contests or other promotions featured on IncrediBots. 

## SECURITY OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

## We take all reasonable precautions to safeguard the privacy of your data.  All data that we collect is stored on one or more secure database servers that cannot be accessed from outside our corporate network. Outside of our network, the only access to this data is that provided through our Web sites. Through our sites, access to personal information is completely controlled by user-defined e-mail addresses and passwords. Within our company, access to data is secured through a private user ID and password known only to personnel who have a need to know such information to perform their essential job functions. All employees of Big Fish Games are legally bound by a nondisclosure agreement that prevents the disclosure of any corporate or customer information to other parties.

## USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

We use your username, e-mail address, and password to uniquely identify you as an IncrediBots user. We may use or display your username for the purposes of rankings, competitions or sweepstakes, message board/chat identification, and/or game high scores.   

If you opt in to receiving our newsletters and e-mail campaigns, we may use your contact information to process our newsletters and/or e-mail campaigns.   Your contact information will allow us to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of site problems, handle and/or route your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, sweepstakes, contests, prizes, and/or special events. 

We use cookies to enhance your online experience.  The information in cookies may enable you to automatically sign in when you visit IncrediBots, and offers other operational site activities. 

We may use other identifying information collected to calculate aggregate statistics about our user community or for security purposes.  

## SHARING INFORMATION

We will not resell your information to any third parties.  We will not share your information with any third parties, except that we may disclose your personal information to third parties who perform services for us.  We do not control the activities of such third party vendors. While we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as Big Fish Games, we will take all reasonable precautions under the circumstances to ensure the protection of your personal information.  We may also disclose your information if there is a violation of the IncrediBots Terms of Use or if we have a good faith belief that the law requires it.  Big Fish Games may provide other aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our user community to partners with whom we do business.

As Big Fish Games continues to grow, we might sell or buy certain business units. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred assets, but would remain subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy (unless you consent otherwise).  Also, in the unlikely event that Big Fish Games or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information would in most cases be one of the transferred assets.

Apart from what is described above, you will receive notice when information about you might otherwise go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share that information.

## E-MAIL/OPT-IN

When you create an IncrediBots account, you may sign up to receive one or more of our newsletters. At any time, you may opt-out of receiving these newsletters by selecting the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any newsletter. Big Fish Games treats each of its consumer offerings individually, so if you are receiving mailings from more than one area of our website, if you want to unsubscribe you must do so with respect to each such area individually. 

## LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

Web sites that link to or from IncrediBots may collect personal information about you. This IncrediBots Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, other Web sites. 

## CHAT & MESSAGING

IncrediBots may operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with each another. When posting to a message board or chat area, the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information posted is the sole responsibility of the individual user. 

**CHILDREN**

## IncrediBots does not offer products for purchase by children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children.  If you are under 13, you may use and access IncrediBots only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

Big Fish Games respects the privacy of parents and children and is committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. **** If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to Big Fish Games, he or she can contact us via e-mail at [privacy@bigfishgames.com](mailto:privacy@bigfishgames.com) or postal mail at the address listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13.  We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of online activities regularly. 

## CONTACT US

## To review, modify or remove the information you have provided to us, or to contact us with any questions or complaints, please e-mail us at [privacy@bigfishgames.com](mailto:privacy@bigfishgames.com) or write to us at: Big Fish Games Legal-Privacy Department, 333 Elliott Avenue West, Suite 200, Seattle, WA 98119\.     

## AGREEMENT WITH BIG FISH GAMES POLICIES

By participating in IncrediBots  and/or using any of our products or services, you signify your understanding of and agreement with this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use. If you do not agree with our policies, please do not use or participate in any of the products or services featured on IncrediBots. 

## CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last modified" date at the top of this page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Big Fish Games protects your information.

|    
---|---|---
